Guide to the Lloyd Richards Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1945-2004; Series V; 2.5; (6 boxes)
  - Photographs of Lloyd Richards
    - "Los Angeles Party", 1991 February 11 (Box 141, Folder 1663)
    - With Paul Mann and Patricia Benoit, 1950s (Box 141, Folder 1664)
    - With the New Dramatists, 1988, undated (Box 141, Folder 1665)
      Includes letter from Jean Passanante
    - "New York Times", 1987 (Box 141, Folder 1666)
    - "Russia", undated (Box 141, Folder 1667)
      Includes negatives
    - "A Salute to Lloyd Richards", 1991 May 13 (Box 141, Folder 1668-1672)
      Includes photos of Mayor Dinkin's reception
    - "A Salute to Lloyd Richards", 1991 May 13 (Box 142, Folder 1673-1675)
    - At Sardi's, 1987 June (Box 142, Folder 1676)
    - Third World Festival International Conference, Philippines, 1971 November (Box 142, Folder 1677)
    - With M. Ulyanov, 1989 July (Box 142, Folder 1678)
    - "Worlds Fair, Switching on Midway", circa 1950 (Box 142, Folder 1679)
    - Yale University Commencement, 1982 May (Box 142, Folder 1680)
      Includes note regarding photographs
    - Yale University President's Reception, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 1681)
    - Yale University School of Drama, undated (Box 142, Folder 1682)
      Includes negatives; slides by Maggie Steber
    - Portraits
      - By Amrando Atkinson, 1989 September 9 (Box 142, Folder 1683)
      - By Virginia Blaisdell, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 1684)
      - By Ruth Fremson, 1997 (Box 142, Folder 1685)
        Includes note to Richards from Ruth Fremson and note from Richards to "Jo Anna"
      - By Gerry Goodstein, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 1686)
      - By Mara Lavitt, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 1687)
      - By Paul Penders, 1984
      - By Sam Wilkins, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 1688)
        Includes letter from Wilkins to Richards
      - "England", 1948 (Box 142, Folder 1689)
      - Unidentified portrait, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 1690)
    - With unidentified friends, undated
      Includes 1996 January 29 letter from Fran Bennett
    - Unidentified, 1979-1992, undated (Box 142, Folder 1691-1696)
      Includes 1979 July 30 letter from Alison Cranmer-Byng and negatives
  - Productions
    - Amen Corner, circa 1965 (Box 143, Folder 1697)
    - An Attempt at Flying, undated (Box 143, Folder 1698)
    - Cobb, 1989 (Box 143, Folder 1699-1701)
    - The Crucible, undated (Box 143, Folder 1702)
    - Fences, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 1703-1704)
    - The Fountain, 1940s (Box 143, Folder 1705)
      Includes letter to Richards from Sydney Spade
    - Gold Watch, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 1706)
    - Hedda Gabler, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 1707)
    - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1986 (Box 143, Folder 1708)
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1987, undated (Box 143, Folder 1709-1713)
      Includes photo album
    - Miss Black America, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 1714)
    - The Moon Besieged, 1962 (Box 143, Folder 1715)
    - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1991 May (Box 143, Folder 1716)
      Includes slides
    - No Easy Walk to Freedom, 1979 (Box 143, Folder 1717)
    - Oedipus Rex, 1946 November (Box 143, Folder 1718)
      Actors Company, Detroit
    - The Piano Lesson, 1987-1988, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 1719-1722)
      Includes portraits with August Wilson and disassembled album of the 1994 production
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 1959 (Box 144, Folder 1723)
      London production
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 1724)
      Reunion at Yale Repertory Theatre, includes portraits of Lloyd Richards
    - Richard III, 1967 (Box 144, Folder 1725-1726)
    - Roots, 1979 (Box 144, Folder 1727-1728)
    - The Rose Tattoo, 1959 (Box 144, Folder 1729)
    - Seven Guitars, 1996 (Box 144, Folder 1730)
      Includes sheet music with note from Dwight Andrews
    - Stevedore: A Play in Three Acts, 1947 (Box 144, Folder 1731)
      Equity Library Theater, New York City.
    - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1957 (Box 144, Folder 1732)
      Northland Playhouse, Southfield, MI
    - Two Trains Running, 1990 (Box 144, Folder 1733)
      Includes portraits with August Wilson and slides
    - Photographs from Yale Repertory Theatre productions directed by Richards, compiled by Gerry Goodstein, 1991 December 20 (Box 144, Folder 1734)
      Disassembled album
    - "Northland Playhouse", 1958 (Box 144, Folder 1735)
    - Unidentified ( Saginaw ), 1954 (Box 145, Folder 1736)
    - Unidentified, 1980s (Box 145, Folder 1737-1738)
  - Awards and Honorary Degree Ceremonies
    - All American Collegiate Golf Foundation, 1989 (Box 145, Folder 1739)
    - American Academy of Achievement, undated (Box 145, Folder 1740)
    - City of New York Mayor's Award of Honor for Arts and Culture, 1988 (Box 145, Folder 1741)
    - City University of New York, 1992 (Box 145, Folder 1742)
    - Mercy College, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1743)
    - National Council on the Arts, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 1744)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 1745)
    - Nation Medal of Art, undated (Box 145, Folder 1746)
    - New York University, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 1747)
    - Northwestern University, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 1748)
    - Princeton University, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 1749)
      Includes 1985 July 23 letter from William Bowen and negatives
    - Rollins College, 1988 (Box 145, Folder 1750)
    - Tony Awards, 1987, 1991,undated (Box 145, Folder 1751-1752)
    - Wayne State University, 1981 (Box 145, Folder 1753)
    - Writers' Guild, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 1754)
    - Unidentified, undated, 1988 (Box 145, Folder 1755-1756)
  - Photographs of Others and Places
    - Lloyd Richards's mother, undated (Box 146, Folder 1757)
    - "Budapest", undated (Box 146, Folder 1758)
    - Great Lakes Summer Festival, undated (Box 146, Folder 1759)
    - "NYU" negatives and contact sheets, undated (Box 146, Folder 1760)
    - Sidney Poitier and Phil Rose, 1950s (Box 146, Folder 1761)
    - "Jason Robards, Jr. recording", 1962 (Box 146, Folder 1762)
    - "Russia", undated (Box 146, Folder 1763)
    - August Wilson, 1987, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 1764-1765)
    - "Yale and New Haven", 1984 (Box 146, Folder 1766-1767)
    - Yale dramaturgs, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 1768)
    - Unidentified, undated, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 1769-1774)
      Includes negatives and slides
    - Unidentified framed portrait, undated
- Personal Papers, 1944-2002; Series VI; 1.83; (5 boxes)
  - U.S. Army Air Corps
    - Training notebooks, 1944-1945 (Box 147, Folder 1775-1777)
    - "Maps, Charts and Aerial Photographs" student's workbook, 1945 (Box 147, Folder 1778)
    - AAF Training Command Provisional Workbooks, 1945 (Box 147, Folder 1779-1780)
      "Primary Navigation" "Basic Navigation" "Primary Equipment"
    - Recognition Handbook for the Pacific and Far East, 1945 (Box 147, Folder 1781)
    - Time distance computer, 1945 (Box 147, Folder 1782)
    - Honorable discharge documents, 1945 (Box 147, Folder 1783)
  - Citizenship documents, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 1784)
    Includes letter from Richards's mother to Richards
  - Financial documents, 1958-2002 (Box 148, Folder 1785-1790)
  - Medical documents, 1975, 1996, 1998 (Box 148, Folder 1791-1793)
    Materials regard Richards's 1975 leave of absence from Hunter College due to health problems
  - Housing documents, 1988, 1992, 2001 (Box 148, Folder 1794-1796)
  - Scott and Betsy's wedding, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 1797)
  - Gay Smith Manifold and Philip Bosakowski wedding program and reading, 1993 May (Box 148, Folder 1798)
  - Board of Elections in the City of New York documents, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 1799)
  - Rolodex with index cards bearing individuals' contact information
    - Casting and A-F, undated (Box 229)
    - G-O, undated (Box 230)
    - P-Z, undated (Box 231)
  - Framed artwork
- Audiovisual Materials, 1962-2004; Series VII; 10.44; (12 boxes)
  This series is arranged into three subseries: Films, Video Recordings and Sound Recordings. The Video Recordings and Sound Recordings subseries is organized under three headings: Productions, Interviews with Lloyd Richards, and Other Recordings. Each folder contains one item.
  Series VII. Audiovisual Materials contains film, video and audio recordings of Richards's productions, interviews with him, and recordings of other programs of interest to Richards.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 149-153 and 161-167 contain audiovisual material. Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Film
    - 8mm unidentified film (2 reels) [8mm color Kodachrome] (Box 161, Folder 1800-1801)
      Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Video Recordings
    All video recordings are VHS and U-matic formats.
    - Productions
      - Fences
        - "Dub", 1988 February 9; JWJMSS176_0001; 1; 00:01:40 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300416)
          Restricted fragile material.
        - "Carole Shorenstein Hays Enterprises", circa 1985; JWJMSS176_0002; 1; 00:51:01 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300424)
      - " Freeman (Visions)" 1 of 2, 1976; JWJMSS176_0049; 1; 00:29:40 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300895)
      - " Freeman (Visions)" 2 of 2, 1976; JWJMSS176_0050; 1; 00:58:19 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300903)
      - " Gold Watch (Visions)" 1 of 2, 1976; JWJMSS176_0051; 1; 01:01:21 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300911)
      - " Gold Watch (Visions)" 2 of 2, 1976; JWJMSS176_0052; 1; 00:26:26 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300929)
      - "Medal of Honor Rag," American Playhouse, Public Television Playhouse Inc, 1 of 2, 1982 February 10; JWJMSS176_0047; 1; 01:15:38 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300879)
      - "Medal of Honor Rag," American Playhouse, Public Television Playhouse Inc, 2 of 2, 1982 February 10; JWJMSS176_0048; 1; 00:36:25 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300887)
      - "Medal Of Honor Rag" 1 of 2, undated; JWJMSS176_0053; 1; 01:02:56 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300937)
      - "Medal Of Honor Rag" 2 of 2, undated; JWJMS176_0054; 1; 00:36:53 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300945)
      - " No Easy Walk to Freedom / Holy War Holy Terror – Shi'ite Muslims", 1979; JWJMSS176_0004; 1; 04:53:02 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300440)
      - "Paul Robeson", 1979 September 8
        - Reel I, Act 1, 1979 September 8; JWJMSS176_0055; 1; 00:58:40 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300952)
        - Reel II, Act 2, 1979 September 8; JWJMSS176_0056; 1; 01:01:59 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300960)
        - Thirteen/WNET, Paul Robeson: Here I Stand, 2 hours, first broadcast, 1999 February 24; JWJMSS176_0003; 1; 01:59:25 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300432)
          There is a typewritten note with the tape dated 1999-03-19. It reads: Dear Mr. Richards, Thank you for your contribution to "Paul Robeson: Here I Stand". Here is a copy of the show. With much appreciation - Kristin Lovejoy.
      - The Piano Lesson
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 2", 1994 September 1; JWJMSS176_0005; 1; 00:25:35 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300457)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 3", 1994 September 2; JWJMSS176_0006; 1; 00:21:24 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300465)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 4", 1994 September 6; JWJMSS176_0007; 1; 00:26:09 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300473)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 8", 1994 September 12; JWJMSS176_0008; 1; 00:57:37; The tape was damaged at approximately 29 minutes into the tape. There is a little video break-up at this point for about 30 seconds. (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300481)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 10", 1994 September 14; YCALMSS366_0009; 1; 01:00:58 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300499)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 11", 1994 September 14; JWJMSS176_0010; 1; 00:15:25 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300507)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 12", 1994 September 15; JWJMSS176_0011; 1; 00:22:52 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300515)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 29", 1994 October 3; JWJMSS176_0012; 1; 00:19:25 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300523)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel Tape 6 Hour 6", 1994 September 8; JWJMSS176_0013; 1; 00:40:58 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300531)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 7", 1994 September 9; JWJMSS176_0014; 1; 00:42:03 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300549)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 9", 1994 September 12; JWJMSS176_0015; 1; 36:01 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300556)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 13", 1994 September 16; JWJMSS176_0016; 1; 01:01:24 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300564)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 15", 1994 September 18; JWJMSS176_0017; 1; 00:57:52 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300572)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 16", 1994 September 18; JWJMSS176_0018; 1; 00:11:47 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300580)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 18", 1994 Sepetmber 20; JWJMSS176_0019; 1; 00:30:51 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300598)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 19", 1994 September 21; JWJMSS176_0020; 1; 00:29:41 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300606)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 21", 1994 September 23; JWJMSS176_0021; 1; 01:00:23 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300614)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 25", 1994 September 28; JWJMSS176_0022; 1; 00:52:02 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300622)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 26", 1994 Sptember 29; JWJMSS176_0023; 1; 00:59:53 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300630)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 28", 1994 October 3; JWJMSS176_0024; 1; 01:00:28 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300648)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 1", 1994 August 31; JWJMSS176_0025; 1; 00:17:48 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300655)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 5", 1994 September 7; JWJMSS176_0026; 1; 00:44:13 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300663)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 14", 1994 September 16; JWJMSS176_0027; 1; 00:47:23 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300671)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 16A", 1994 September 19; JWJMSS176_0028; 1; 01:00:39 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300689)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 17", 1994 September 19; JWJMSS176_0029; 1; 00:39:59 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300697)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 20 / Cam roll A108-A114", 1994 September 22; JWJMSS176_0030; 1; 00:59:29 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300705)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 22", 1994 September 26; JWJMSS176_0031; 1; 00:59:15 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300713)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 23", 1994 September 26; JWJMSS176_0032; 1; 00:45:10 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300721)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions (71,4,2) Numbered reels/ Dailies, reel 24", 1994 September 27; JWJ MSS 176_0033; 1; 00:39:10 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300739)
        - "Piano Lesson" Director's Rough Cut #2", 1994 October 13; JWJMSS176_0034; 1; 01:50:03 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300747)
        - "Editor's Cut", 1994 October 7; JWJMSS176_0035; 1; 02:43:17 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002102300754)
        - "Producer's Cut", 1994 October 21; JWJMSS176_0036; 1; 01:40:49 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300762)
        - "Signboard Hill Productions – Director's Cut", 1994 November 2; JWJMSS176_0037; 1; 01:41:53 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300770)
        - "Hallmark Hall of Fame Productions, Viewing cassette, parts 1 & 2 tied", 1994; JWJMSS176_0038; 1; 01:47:07 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300788)
        - "Hallmark Hall of Fame Presentation will air Sunday Feb 5 1995 on CBS", 1995 February 5; JWJMSS176_0039; 1; 01:39:54 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300796)
        - "Press coverage reel", 1990 May 14; JWJMSS176_0040; 1; 00:18:38 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300804)
        - "Backstage at the The Goodman Theatre", 1989; JWJMSS176_0041; 1; 00:18:38 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300812)
        - "August Wilson's The Piano Lesson at the Goodman Theater", 1989 January 22; JWJMSS176_0042; 1; 02:42:24 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300820)
          A typewritten note to Lloyd Richards from Richard Pettengill of The Goodman Theatre dated 1989-04-11. It reads: Dear Lloyd, Here is a copy of the entire performance of The Piano Lesson. The reproduction quality is not what I'd like it to be, but I hope it's useful to you nonetheless. The original is stored here in our archives. I've also sent a copy to August. I hope you received my recent letter about my interest in serving as a dramaturg at the O'Neill. I look forward to hearing back from you when you have a chance. Best regards, Richard Pettengill.
        - "The Piano Lesson", undated; JWJMSS176_0043; 1; 01:40:53 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300838)
        - "Backstage at the Goodman", 1989; 1; 00:20:01; There are hits on the tape at 7:00 and 16:53. (Box 150, Item barcode 39002104618195)
          Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        - "The Piano Lesson, 22", undated; 1; 01:41:19 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002104618203)
        - "The Piano Lesson, 23", undated; 1; 01:41:04 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002104618211)
        - "The Piano Lesson", Hallmark Hall of Fame Presentation, 1995; 1; 01:40:41 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002104618229)
      - " The Resurrection of Lady Lester, Act 1, CBS Cable", 1982 April 26; JWJMSS176_0057; 1; 00:45:27 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300978)
        A note from John Musilli to Lloyd Richards, dated 1982-06-23, reads: Lloyd - Here's the long overdue cassette of "Lady Lester" - sorry for the delay!
      - " The Resurrection of Lady Lester, Acts 2 and 3, CBS Cable", 1982; JWJMSS176_0058; 1; 00:44:11 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300986)
      - The Roots: The Next Generation
        - Roots II, Show 6, Part 1, ABC, 1979; JWJMSS176_0059; 1; 00:59:28 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102300994)
        - Roots II, Show 6, Part 2, ABC, 1979; JWJMSS176_0060; 1; 00:38:30 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102301000)
        - Roots II, Show 6, Reel 1 (Duplicate), undated; 1
        - Roots II, Show 6, Reel 2 (Duplicate), 1
      - Two Trains Running
        - "Backstage at the Goodman", 1993 February; JWJMSS196_0044; 1; 00:19:06 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300846)
        - "Interviews", circa 1991; JWJMSS176_0045; 1; 02:50:56; The sound is very low and in poor quality. (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300853)
          A typewritten note, dated 1992-08-31, from Jeff Richards and David LeShay (of Jeffrey Richards Associates) to Lloyd Richards is included. It reads: We thought you would like to have a copy of the enclosed videotape which has most of the television interviews arranged for "Two Trains Running" on Broadway. This tape includes the following: Enjoy!
          August Wilson on "The Charlie Rose Show" (WNET)
          Larry Fishburne on "Good Morning America" (ABC)
          August Wilson on "The Dick Cavett Show" (CNBC)
          Larry Fishburne on "Showbiz Today" (CNN)
          Roscoe Lee Browne on "The McCreary Report" (FOX)
          Lloyd Richards on "The Charlie Rose Show" (WNET)
          Larry Fishburne on "The Arsenio Hall Show" (Syndicated)
          Lloyd Richards on "Inside Business" (CNN)
          Roscoe Lee Browne on "News at Five" (WCBS)
          Roscoe Lee Browne on "The Charlie Rose Show" (WNET)
          Larry Fishburne with Pia Lindstrom (WNBC)
          Larry Fishburne on "Live with Regis and Kathie Lee" (Syndicated)
          Larry Fishburne's Tony Awards acceptance speech
          Roscoe Lee Browne on "Live with Regis and Kathie Lee" (Syndicated)
        - "Audition Tape 1. John Beasley- Mr. West 2. Ernest Perry Jr.- Mr. West ", undated; JWJMSS176_0046; 1 (Box 150, Item barcode 39002102300861)
          This tape was not digitized. The contents do not relate to the label description.
        - "Two Trains Running"/Director: Lloyd Richards, circa 1991; JWJ MSS 176_0107; 1; 00:43:00 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672773)
    - Interviews with Lloyd Richards
      - "Lloyd Richards interview with Natasha Krimova O'Neill Theater Center", 1988 July 9; JWJMSS176_0064; 1; 00:34:19 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002102301042)
      - "Sunday Morning: Lloyd Richards", 1987 May 3; JWJMSS176_0106; 1; 00:11:13 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672765)
      - "American Theatre Wing's Guide to Careers in the Theatre: Lloyd Richards, Director", 2001 October 26; JWJMSS176_0108; 1; 00:56:18 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672781)
        A note written by Roy A. Somlyo of the American Theatre Wing is included. It reads: Lloyd - Here is a copy of that wonderful interview you did for our career guide series. Thanks again - You should love it, we do! All the best for the holidays to you and Barbara. Roy
      - "Lloyd Richards interview with Natasha Krimova 7/88 "Horizons Beyond… The O'Neill" Demo rough cut", 1988 September; JWJMSS176_0112; 1; 00:39:18 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672823)
        There is a typewritten note, dated 1988-10-27, from Kim T. Eveleth of the Eugene O'Neill Theater Center. It reads: Dear Lloyd: Enclosed is a VHS video tape copy of your interview with Natasha Krimova in its entirety for your archives. As per your request, it has not been edited. It was originally shot on two tapes, and I have indicated the point on your copy where the second tape begins. I have also included the first rough cut edited for demonstration purposes from the footage taped over the summer. As I mentioned in our phone conversation, this demo tape is being shown to Potential funders for Horizons Beyond...The O'Neill. Since I had only one day to edit, the tape is focused on some of the people we interviewed this summer and some of the ideas they presented, rather than a medly of images. So far it has been very well received. I trust you'll be pleased with the results. Thank you for all your help and support on Horizons Beyond.... Cordially, Kim
      - "The History Makers: Lloyd Richards (dub from Beta Original Rolls 1-4)", 2001-09-13; JWJMSS176_0113; 1; 01:16:37 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672849)
      - "The History Makers: Lloyd Richards (dub from Beta Original Rolls 5-8)", 2001-09-13; JWJMSS176_0114; 1; 02:02:15 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672831)
      - "Meet the Playwright: Lloyd Richards, DCTC Stage Theatre", 2000 January 3; JWJMSS176_0115; 1; 01:18:30 (Box 153, Item barcode 39002093672856)
        A handwritten note from Sylvie from the Denver Center for the Performing Arts, dated 2000-03-21, is included with the tape. It reads: Dear Lloyd, As promised, here is your tape. Remember it's for archival use only. Enclosed too is a photo you might enjoy - Hope your little fella is doing beautifully! Sylive